export const math = [  
    {   
        "sr" : 1,
        "question" : "What is correct answer of - 3 + 6 x (5 + 4) ÷ 3 ?",
        "options" : ["21","27","54","81"],
        "correct" : "a"
    },
    {
        "sr" : 2,
        "question" : "What is next term in series of - 4, 6, 12, 14, 28, 30, (?)",
        "options" : [
        "62",
        "64",
        "60",
        "32"
        ],
        "correct" : "c"
    },
    {
        "sr" : 3,
        "question" : "Who is the Father of Mathematics?",
        "options" : [
            "Aryabhatt",
            "Archimedes",
        "Acharya Chanakya",
        "Rishi Bhrigu"
        ],
        "correct" : "b"
    },
    {
        "sr" : 4,
        "question" : "What is the area of Triangle ?",
        "options" : [
            "3 × side of triangle",
            "1/2 (base × height)",
        "base × height",
        "None of them"
        ],
        "correct" : "b"
    },
    {
        "sr" : 5,
        "question" : "What is the sum of interior angle of pentagon ?",
        "options" : [
        "360 deg",
        "720 deg",
        "100 deg",
        "540 deg"
        ],
        "correct" : "d"
    },
    {
        "sr" : 6,
        "question" : "In parallelogram opposite sides are ?",
        "options" : [
        "Only Equal",
        "Equal and Parallel",
        "Parallel only",
        "Unequal and not parallel"
        ],
        "correct" : "b"
    },
    {
        "sr" : 7,
        "question" : "What is the value of Pie (π) ?",
        "options" : [
        "3.14159",
        "21/7",
        "3.9",
        "Not found",
        ],
        "correct" : "a"
    },
    {
        "sr" : 8,
        "question" : "What is the roman of 150 ?",
        "options" : [
        "DL",
        "LM",
        "CL",
        "CXXXXX",
        ],
        "correct" : "c"
    },
    {
        "sr" : 9,
        "question" : "Identify Prime Number in the following -",
        "options" : [
        "0",
        "25",
        "33",
        "29"
        ],
        "correct" : "d"
    },
    {
        "sr" : 10,
        "question" : "Degree of quadratic equation is ?",
        "options" : [
        "2",
        "3",
        "1",
        "None of these"
        ],
        "correct" : "a"
    }
]